Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Executive Office Records, 1951-1999; 28490
  - Subseries II:B: Lillian Roberts Associate Director Records, 1951-1983., 28491
    - New York City HHC: Education and Training, 1977-1978; cuid4855; 28629 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - New York City HHC: Education Programs, 1972-1975; cuid4856; 28628 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - New York City HHC: Emergency Medical Service (EMS), 1977; cuid4857; 28627 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - New York City HHC: EMS, 1978; cuid4858; 28626 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - New York City HHC: EMS Manhattan Plan, 1978-1982; cuid4859; 28625 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - New York City HHC: Ethnic Census, 1970; cuid4860; 28624 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - New York City HHC: Financial Plan Data, 1978; cuid4861; 28623 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - New York City HHC: Functional Program and Space Utilization Study, 1976; cuid4862; 28622 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - New York City HHC: Gouverneur Hospital Closing, 1976; cuid4863; 28621 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - New York City HHC: Joint Labor-Management Productivity Committee, Aug 1976-Mar 1977; cuid4864; 28620 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - New York City HHC: Joint Labor-Management Productivity Committee, Apr 1977-Sep 1978; cuid4865; 28619 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - New York City HHC: Labor-Management Conferences, 1970-1971; cuid4866; 28618 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - New York City HHC: Layoff Analysis, 1976; cuid4867; 28617 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - New York City HHC: Medicaid Reimbursements (New York State Office of Health Systems Management), 1978; cuid4868; 28616 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - New York City HHC: Patient Accounting Proposal, 1977; cuid4869; 28615 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - New York City HHC: Personnel and Layoffs, 1975; cuid4870; 28614 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - New York City HHC: Personnel Review Board Decisions, 1978-1979; cuid4871; 28613 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - New York City HHC: Press Releases, 1970-1977; cuid4872; 28612 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - New York City HHC: Productivity Committee, Cost of Living Adjustment (COLA) I, 1977-1978; cuid4873; 28611 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - New York City HHC: Productivity Committee, Cost of Living Adjustment (COLA) II, 1977-1978; cuid4874; 28610 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - New York City HHC: Productivity Program, 1977; cuid4875; 28609 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - New York City HHC: Productivity Working Papers, 1976-1977; cuid4876; 28608 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - New York City HHC: Productivity Working Papers, 1978; cuid4877; 28607 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - New York City HHC: Professional Division (Local 1407), 1970; cuid4878; 28606 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - New York City HHC: Rollbacks, 1967-1973; cuid4879; 28605 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - New York City HHC: Roosevelt Island Laundry Closing, 1974-1975; cuid4880; 28604 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - New York City HHC: Taylor Law Application (1976 Strike), 1970, 1976-1978; cuid4881; 28603 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - New York City HHC: Training Coalition, 1970-1971; cuid4882; 28602 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - New York City HHC: Training Program for Billing/Collecting, 1971-1972; cuid4883; 28601 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - New York City HHC: Tripartite Task Force on Potential Additional Sources of Revenue and Decentralization, Jul 1976; cuid4884; 28600 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - New York City HHC: Basic Education Program, 1970; cuid4885; 28599 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - New York City Housing and Development Administration (HDA), undated, 1977-1978; cuid4886; 28598 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - New York City HDA: Community Liaison Workers (Local 371), 1977-1979; cuid4887; 28597 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - New York City HDA: Support Service Contracts, 1978-1979; cuid4888; 28596 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - New York City Human Resources Administration, 1976-1979; cuid4889; 28595 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - New York City Juvenile Justice Agency, 1979; cuid4890; 28594 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - New York City Manual of Personnel Policies, undated; cuid4891; 28593 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - New York City Medical School Proposal, Jun 1972-Oct 1973; cuid4892; 28592 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - New York City Medical School Proposal, Feb 1974-Jul 1975; cuid4893; 28591 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - New York City Office of Labor Relations, 1973-1975; cuid4894; 28590 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - New York City Unemployed and Welfare Council, 1978; cuid4895; 28589 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - New York State Advisory Council on Substance Abuse, 1976-1980; cuid4896; 28588 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - New York State Department of Civil Service: Title and Salary Plan I, 1968; cuid4897; 28587 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - New York State Department of Civil Service: Title and Salary Plan II, 1968; cuid4898; 28586 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - New York State Department of Mental Hygiene: Inventory of Inservice Training Courses, 1966; cuid4899; 28585 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - New York State Division of Substance Abuse Services, 1980; cuid4900; 28584 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - New York State Employment and Training Council, 1979-1980; cuid4901; 28583 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - New York Urban Coalition, 1980-1981; cuid4902; 28582 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - New York Urban Coalition: Health Manpower Committee, 1969-1970; cuid4903; 28581 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - North Brooklyn Hospital Training Project, 1972-1974; cuid4904; 28580 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - North Brooklyn Hospital Training Project (Woodhull Hospital): Proposal to Train Community Residents for Professional Positions, 1972-1973; cuid4905; 28579 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - North Central Bronx Hospital, 1973-1974; cuid4906; 28578 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - North Central Bronx Hospital, 1975; cuid4907; 28577 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - North Central Bronx Hospital, 1976; cuid4908; 28576 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Nurse's Aide to Licensed Practical Nurse (LPN) Upgrading Program, 1967-1968; cuid4909; 28575 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program, Jan 1969-May 1969; cuid4910; 28574 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program, Jun 1969-Dec 1969; cuid4911; 28573 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Instruction for Blood Pressure, 1968; cuid4912; 28572 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Instruction on Vocational Adjustment I, 1968; cuid4913; 28571 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Instruction on Vocational Adjustment II, 1968; cuid4914; 28570 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Printed Material and Publicity, 1967-1969; cuid4915; 28569 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, 1967; cuid4916; 28568 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, 1967-1968; cuid4917; 28567 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, Feb 1968-Jun 1968; cuid4918; 28566 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, Jun 1968-Nov 1968; cuid4919; 28565 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, Nov 1968-Apr 1969; cuid4920; 28564 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, Apr 1969-Sep 1969; cuid4921; 28563 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, Sep 1969-Dec 1969; cuid4922; 28562 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 153, 1970; cuid4923; 28561 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Outside Activities, 1967-1971; cuid4924; 28560 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Personal Services Unit, 1970-1973; cuid4925; 28559 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Personnel Issues, 1969; cuid4926; 28558 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Personnel Issues, 1970-1972; cuid4927; 28557 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Personnel Issues, 1973; cuid4928; 28556 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Personnel Issues, 1974-1975; cuid4929; 28555 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Personnel Issues, 1976-1977; cuid4930; 28554 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Personnel Policies and Procedures, 1974-1976; cuid4931; 28553 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Pipeline Correspondence, 1971; cuid4932; 28552 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Political Action: Governor's Race (Rockefeller/Goldberg), 1970; cuid4933; 28551 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Productivity in City Agencies, 1972-1975; cuid4934; 28550 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Professional and Cultural Division: Monthly Staff Reports (Lubin, Castiglione, McCabe, Trotter, Hill, Shaplo, Baron), 1974-1975; cuid4935; 28549 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Public Service Employment Conference, 1973; cuid4936; 28548 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Queens General Hospital, 1976; cuid4937; 28547 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Reich, Chaim B., M.D., 1978; cuid4938; 28546 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: Health Services Mobility Study (HSMS) Plan of Work, 1968; cuid4939; 28545 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 1, "Train Practical Nurses to Become Registered Nurses" (Draft), 1968; cuid4940; 28544 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 1, "Train Practical Nurses to Become Registered Nurses: A Survey of the PN Point of View", 1968; cuid4941; 28543 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 2, Vol. 1, "Occupational Structure of New York City Municipal Hospitals" (Draft)", 1969; cuid4942; 28542 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 2, Vol. 2, "Occupational Structure of New York City Municipal Hospitals" (Draft), 1969; cuid4943; 28541 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 2, "Occupational Structure of New York City Municipal Hospitals, Volume 1", 1969; cuid4944; 28540 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 2, "Occupational Structure of New York City Municipal Hospitals, Volume 2", 1969; cuid4945; 28539 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Reports Nos. 4 and 5, "Suggestions for Job and Curriculum Ladders in Health Center Ambulatory Care", 1972; cuid4946; 28538 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Second Progress Report, 1969; cuid4947; 28537 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Technical Report No. 2, 1968; cuid4948; 28536 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Technical Report No. 4, 1969; cuid4949; 28535 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Technical Report No. 7, 1970; cuid4950; 28534 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Technical Report Nos. 8-9, 1970; cuid4951; 28533 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Technical Report Nos. 10-11, 1971-1972; cuid4952; 28532 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Working Paper No. 2, "A Pre-Test Manual for Task Identification", 1968; cuid4953; 28531 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Working Paper No. 4, "A Pre-Test Manual for Task Identification (Re-Test)", 1969; cuid4954; 28530 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Working Paper No. 7, "A Re-Test Manual for Scaling Task Dimensions", 1970; cuid4955; 28529 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Roberts, Lillian, undated, 1971-1972, 1983; cuid4956; 28528 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Safety Issues, 1978-1979; cuid4957; 28527 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Safety Training, 1974-1975; cuid4958; 28526 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - School Decentralization, 1969; cuid4959; 28525 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - School Volunteer Program, 1976; cuid4960; 28524 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Schools Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Apr 1974-Jun 1974; cuid4961; 28523 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Schools Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Jul 1974-Feb 1975; cuid4962; 28522 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Schools Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Mar 1975-Jul 1976; cuid4963; 28521 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Seaview Hospital, undated; cuid4964; 28520 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Segundo Ruiz Belvis Neighborhood Family Care Center, 1976; cuid4965; 28519 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Society for Advanced Medical Systems (SAMS), 1978; cuid4966; 28518 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Speaking Engagements and Speeches, undated, 1970-1971; cuid4967; 28517 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Speaking Engagements and Speeches, 1972-1979; cuid4968; 28516 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Speaking Engagements and Speeches: RAND Institute, Job Enrichment, 1973; cuid4969; 28515 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - State University of New York: Board of Trustees, 1979-1980; cuid4970; 28514 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Stationary Firemen, 1971; cuid4971; 28513 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Surgical Group Practice, Bellevue Hospital, 1971; cuid4972; 28512 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Sydenham Hospital, 1974-1976; cuid4973; 28511 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Sydenham Hospital, 1976-1978; cuid4974; 28510 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Sydenham Hospital, 1980; cuid4975; 28509 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Television Series, 1971; cuid4976; 28508 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Trade Union Committee to Restore Welfare, Medicaid, and School Lunch Cuts I, 1969-1970; cuid4977; 28507 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Trade Union Committee to Restore Welfare, Medicaid, and School Lunch Cuts II, 1969-1970; cuid4978; 28506 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - United States Census, 1980; cuid4979; 28505 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare: State Health Careers Councils and Committees Workshop, 1966; cuid4980; 28504 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, 1977; cuid4981; 28503 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - White Collar Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Apr 1974-Sep 1974; cuid4982; 28502 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - White Collar Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Oct 1974-Feb 1975; cuid4983; 28501 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - White Collar Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Mar 1975-Aug 1975; cuid4984; 28500 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Wildcat Services Corporation (Vera Institute of Justice), 1973-1977; cuid4985; 28499 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Women's Political Training Center, Hunter College: Advisory Board, 1977-1978; cuid4986; 28498 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Woodhull Hospital, 1978; cuid4987; 28497 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Woodhull Hospital: Mayor's Committee on Woodhull Report, 1978; cuid4988; 28496 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Work in America Institute: National Advisory Committee, 1979-1980; cuid4989; 28495 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Work Incentive Program (WIN) and New York Work Rules, ca.1970, 1971; cuid4990; 28494 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Work Relief Employment Program (WREP): Post-Certification, 1974-1975; cuid4991; 28493 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Workmen's Compensation, 1978-1979; cuid4992; 28492 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Series III: Legal Department Records, 1956-1986; 28274
  - AFSCME Attorney's Conference, 1983; cuid4993; 28489 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, Community and Social Agency Employees Union (CSAE): Agreements, 1979; cuid4994; 28488 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Agreements, 1979-1981; cuid4995; 28487 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Agreements, 1981; cuid4996; 28486 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Agreements, 1982; cuid4997; 28485 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Agreements, 1982-1983; cuid4998; 28484 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Constitution and Related Correspondence, undated, 1980-1984; cuid4999; 28483 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Proposed Merger with DC 37 I, 1984; cuid5000; 28482 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Proposed Merger with DC 37 II, 1984; cuid5001; 28481 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Proposed Merger with DC 37 III, 1984; cuid5002; 28480 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Proposed Merger with DC 37, Background Material, 1984; cuid5003; 28479 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Board of Education v. Vincent J. Byrne: Affidavits, 1975, 1977; cuid5004; 28478 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Background Materials, 1963-1976; cuid5005; 28477 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Court Papers, 1975-1977; cuid5006; 28476 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Exhibits, 1975-1977; cuid5007; 28475 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Memoranda and Correspondence, 1975-1977; cuid5008; 28474 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Notes, 1977; cuid5009; 28473 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Transcripts I, 1976-1977; cuid5010; 28472 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Transcripts II, 1976-1977; cuid5011; 28471 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Transcripts III, 1976-1977; cuid5012; 28470 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Transcripts IV, 1976-1977; cuid5013; 28469 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Transcripts (Partial), ca.1977; cuid5014; 28468 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Butler, James (Local 420) v. DC 37: Accounting, ca.1979; cuid5015; 28467 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavit, James Butler, 1979; cuid5016; 28466 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavit, Lester Wright, 1979; cuid5017; 28465 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavit, Lillian Roberts, 1978-1979; cuid5018; 28464 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavit, Victor Gotbaum, 1978-1979; cuid5019; 28463 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavits, 1979; cuid5020; 28462 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavits, Local 420 Members, 1979; cuid5021; 28461 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Appellate Division Arguments, Notes, 1979; cuid5022; 28460 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Background Materials, 1979; cuid5023; 28459 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Charges against DC 37 Members, 1979; cuid5024; 28458 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Commission to Take Deposition, 1979; cuid5025; 28457 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Constitution and Financial Standards Codes, DC 37 and Local 420, 1971, 1975, 1978; cuid5026; 28456 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Depositions, 1979; cuid5027; 28455 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Depositions, Local 420 Members, 1979; cuid5028; 28454 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Discovery, 1978-1979; cuid5029; 28453 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Drafts, ca.1979; cuid5030; 28452 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Hospital Crisis and May 1st Rally, 1979; cuid5031; 28451 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Local 420 Members' Petition, 1979; cuid5032; 28450 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Notes and Research, 1979; cuid5033; 28449 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Order to Show Cause, Butler Deposition, 1979; cuid5034; 28448 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Order to Show Cause, O'Malley Deposition, 1979; cuid5035; 28447 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings I, 1979; cuid5036; 28446 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings II, 1979; cuid5037; 28445 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings III, 1979; cuid5038; 28444 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings IV, 1979; cuid5039; 28443 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings V, 1979; cuid5040; 28442 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings VI, 1979; cuid5041; 28441 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings VII, 1979; cuid5042; 28440 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings VIII, 1979; cuid5043; 28439 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings IX, 1979; cuid5044; 28438 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings X, 1979; cuid5045; 28437 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings XI, 1979; cuid5046; 28436 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Preliminary Injunction, 1979; cuid5047; 28435 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Protective Order and Appeal, 1979; cuid5048; 28434 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Reply Brief, 1979; cuid5049; 28433 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Summary of Argument, ca.1979; cuid5050; 28432 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Summaries and Complaint, 1979; cuid5051; 28431 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Temporary Restraining Order, 1979; cuid5052; 28430 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - City Civil Service Commission, 1982; cuid5053; 28429 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Citywide Bargaining: Deferral Payment Agreement and Comparison Agreement I, 1982-1983; cuid5054; 28428 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Citywide Bargaining: Deferral Payment Agreement and Comparison Agreement II, 1982-1983; cuid5055; 28427 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Citywide Bargaining: Deferral Payment Agreement and Comparison Agreement, Drafts I, 1982-1983; cuid5056; 28426 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Citywide Bargaining: Deferral Payment Agreement and Comparison Agreement, Drafts II, 1982-1983; cuid5057; 28425 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Citywide Bargaining: Municipal Coalition Economic Agreement, Drafts, 1982-1983; cuid5058; 28424 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - DC 37 and CUNY, Board of Higher Education Arbitration (Eugene Sanjour Case): Background Materials, 1968-1977; cuid5059; 28423 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - DC 37 and CUNY, Board of Higher Education Arbitration (Sanjour Case): Correspondence, 1975-1978; cuid5060; 28422 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - DC 37 and CUNY, Board of Higher Education Arbitration (Sanjour Case): Legal Papers, 1977-1978; cuid5061; 28421 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - DC 37 and CUNY, Board of Higher Education Arbitration (Sanjour Case): Notes, ca.1977; cuid5062; 28420 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. New York Police Department (NYPD): Transcripts I, 1980; cuid5063; 28419 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. NYPD: Transcripts II, 1980; cuid5064; 28418 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. NYPD: Transcripts III, 1980; cuid5065; 28417 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. NYPD: Transcripts IV, 1980; cuid5066; 28416 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. NYPD: Transcripts V, 1980; cuid5067; 28415 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. NYPD: Transcripts VI, 1980; cuid5068; 28414 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - DC 37 v. Commission of Investigation of the State of New York (SIC) (Release Time Program Case): Affidavit of Cause, 1981; cuid5069; 28413 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Background Material, 1973-1981; cuid5070; 28412 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Background Material, Legal I, undated, 1975; cuid5071; 28411 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Background Material, Legal II, undated, 1975; cuid5072; 28410 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Correspondence, 1957-1982; cuid5073; 28409 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Decision, 1982; cuid5074; 28408 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Legal Drafts, undated; cuid5075; 28407 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Legal Drafts, 1981; cuid5076; 28406 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Compel, Memoranda in Opposition, 1981; cuid5077; 28405 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Compel, Memoranda in Support, 1981; cuid5078; 28404 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Compel, Reply Briefs, 1981; cuid5079; 28403 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Quash, Affidavits in Opposition, 1981; cuid5080; 28402 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Quash, Affidavits in Support, 1981; cuid5081; 28401 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Quash, Memoranda in Opposition, 1981; cuid5082; 28400 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Quash, Memoranda in Support, 1981; cuid5083; 28399 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Municipal Labor Committee (MLC) Member List, ca.1981; cuid5084; 28398 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Order to Show Cause, 1981; cuid5085; 28397 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: SIC Annual Reports, 1961-1979; cuid5086; 28396 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Subpoenae, 1981; cuid5087; 28395 (Box 33, Folder 12)